

SHIFIN NIHAD KK

CAPTURE THE ATTENTION OF AUDIENCES

MY OBJECTIVE

"I am a creative motion graphic designer and 2D animator with two years of experience. With a passion for storytelling and visual communication. I always looking for new creative challenges and opportunities to expand their skill set. They are excited to bring their passion and expertise to a new project or team."

INDIA NATIONALITY

16.10.1999 (23)

80% 100%

50%

ENGLISH MALAYALAM LANGUAGE

HINDI

CONTACT



EDUCATION

95 444 584 35 MOBILE NUMBER

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018-2021 **B.A Multimedia**

Gems Arts And Science College, Ramapuram

2018 Jewellery cad designing (2 months training)

Institute of Gems & Jewellery, Inkel edu city,

malappuram

2016-2018 Additional Skill Acquisition Programme

Higher Education Department, Govt. of Kerala

2016-2018 Higher Education

Govt. Higher Secondary School Irumbuzhi

EXPERTISE

After effects

Illustrator

Photoshop

Premier pro

Blender

Autodesk maya

Adobe Flash

Capio Interactive, Calicut

Motion Graphics, 2D Animation, Video Editing.

Spar Stores commercial Company & Al Sadhan Trading company, Saudi Arabia

Video Editing & Animation Designing.

Iluzia Lab, Govt. Cyberpark, Calicut

Motion Graphics, 2D Animation, Social Media Ads, Project Handling.

Owl media (freelance)

Motion Graphics, Logo Animation, Graphics, Logo Designing, Social Media Ads.

PHOTOGRAPHY
TRAVELLING MUSIC COLOURS
MOVIES 2D,3D-ANIMATION
BACKGROUND MUSIC
FOOTBALL Graphics
FRIENDS VIDEO TYPOGRAPHY
MOTION VIDEOS